<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="recipeLuxuryDishes">
        <item>Delicious avocado soup with cooked crab</item>
        <item>Beef rolled with baked potato and vegetables</item>
        <item>Exotic coquilles with a light dressing</item>
        <item>Rich flavoured crab-soup</item>
        <item>Soft white fish with orange caviar eggs</item>
        <item>Sweet rice with sauteded onions and light sweet dressing</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="forAmountOfPeopleLuxuryDishes">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>4</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="caloriesLuxuryDishes">
        <item>250</item>
        <item>180</item>
        <item>280</item>
        <item>320</item>
        <item>400</item>
        <item>290</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cookingTimeLuxuryDishes">
        <item>45</item>
        <item>80</item>
        <item>50</item>
        <item>40</item>
        <item>40</item>
        <item>25</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="descriptionLuxuryDishes">
        <item>Overpriced avocado soup with cooked crab. Altough it is delicious it is pricy and hard to make. But the ingrediënts
        needed are: - Avocado - Salt - Pepper - Lobster - Maizena</item>
        <item>Rolled beef with baked potatoes and smored vegetables. This delicious meal takes alot of time but is worth in the
        long end. Items needed to make this dish are: - Potatoes - Beef - Basel - Carrots - Salt - Pepper - Brocolli</item>
        <item>Exotic coquilles with a light dressing. This dish is hard to master, but once done. Very delicious. Items needed are:
        - Scalps - Wine dressing - Basel - Bread - Salt - Pepper</item>
        <item>Rich and delicious flavoured crab-soup. This soup is for whealthy people. If you make it. You will never want something
        else. Ingrediënts needed: - Juice of a crab - Cooked crab - Salt - Pepper</item>
        <item>Soft and very good white fish. Served with asparagus and orange caviar. This expensive and delicious meal can be made
        with the following ingrediënts: - White fish - Asparagus - Salt - Pepper - Orange caviar eggs</item>
        <item>Sweet and low fat rice with sauteded onions. This meal is for the master cooks. Master all cooking steps to make
        the perfect rice. Items needed for this great dish are: - Rice - Onions - Dressing - Basel - Bread</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>